Hi, and welcome to this course. I am so excited to have you here, and I want to make sure you get the most value out of this course
The course is divided into two sections
Section 1 takes you from not knowing anything about MCP to building your first MCP server in Python
If everyone at work is talking about MCP, but you have no idea what it is then this section is for you
You will learn how to connect LLM to external applications and API and then you will be using cloud disktop to connect to your MCP server
Once you finish off with the foundation
Section 2 shifts your mindset to a security engineer or penetration tester or even a software engineer
You will start seeing MCP servers as targets to attacks. We will exploit the most common vulnerabilities in MCP servers
And you will learn how to attack MCP servers prompt injection in a chatbot application and much more
If you are already familiar with MCP and you have built local and remote MCP servers before
Then you can immediately skip section 1 and jump immediately to section 2
However, I still recommend you to at least skim through section 1 to ensure you have the right foundation
I wish I had a course like this when I started my journey in learning MCP
So I am so excited to share my knowledge with you. Alright, let's get started and I will see you in the next lecture. Thanks for watching